<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="accessibility_enabled">Acessibilidade activada</string>
  <string name="agree">Concordar</string>
  <string name="agree_and_next">Concordar</string>
  <string name="agree_terms">Eu li e aceitei os Termos de Serviço e Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="album_introduction">A Galeria permite gerir, optimizar e editar fotos e vídeos no seu dispositivo, assim como, sincronizá-los na Xiaomi Cloud</string>
  <string name="app_name">Configuração</string>
  <string name="application_package_introduction">Esta aplicação permite instalar aplicações de terceiros, analisá-las antes da instalação e dar recomendações após</string>
  <string name="application_permissions">Permissões da aplicação</string>
  <string name="back">Voltar</string>
  <string name="calculator_introduction">You can use this app for calculations, converting units and currencies, and estimating your mortgage repayments.</string>
  <string name="camera_introduction">You can use Camera to take photos and shoot videos.</string>
  <string name="carrier_introduction">"In order to provide you with better services, your device may periodically send your device version information, device identification data (including IMEI/IMSI/MSISDN/MAC address, MEID/ICCID), and approximate location information (including base station ID) to the carrier via Wi-Fi, mobile data network, or free SMS. The carrier promises to analyze relevant information only to improve the quality of services or to provide customized services or technologies, and won't disclose relevant information to third parties in any form that identifies you personally. The specific carrier statement shall prevail. Consult your carrier regarding the cost of using this service."</string>
  <string name="clock_introduction">You can use this app to view time, as well as use timer, world clock, stopwatch, set alarms, and more.</string>
  <string name="close_location_service_setting">You can choose turn off location access in Settings &gt; Additional settings &gt; Privacy or restrict permissions for individual apps in Security.</string>
  <string name="cm_terms_content">"In order to improve the services provided to you, the mobile network operator of your choice may upload your personal data and the info about this device to its servers using Wi-Fi networks or mobile data connection. This information will only be used for statistical purposes in order to improve the quality of the services and provide more personalized content. This information won't be used to identify you personally and won't be disclosed to third parties."</string>
  <string name="cm_terms_title">Mobile Network Operator Agreement</string>
  <string name="compass_introduction">You can use this app for navigation, as well as viewing coordinates, atmospheric pressure, and altitude.</string>
  <string name="congratulation_label">Tudo pronto para começar!</string>
  <string name="congratulation_swipe">Deslize para cima para entrar no sistema</string>
  <string name="congratulation_title">Configuração concluída</string>
  <string name="content_description_complete">Concluído</string>
  <string name="content_description_miui_version">MIUI 11</string>
  <string name="content_description_start">Iniciar</string>
  <string name="content_introduction">Content Center aggregates content and services from multiple channels. Here you can read articles, watch videos, view daily featured items, and receive content recommendations.</string>
  <string name="continue_to_enable_accessibility">Mantenha premido dois dedos para activar a acessibilidade</string>
  <string name="desc_fingerprint">Utilize a sua impressão digital para desbloquear o seu dispositivo, para verificar as transações de Mi Pay ou para iniciar sessão em aplicações e serviços</string>
  <string name="desc_international_fingerprint">Utilize a sua impressão digital para desbloquear o seu dispositivo ou para iniciar sessão em aplicações e serviços</string>
  <string name="diagnose_report">Send diagnostic data to locate and analyze system issues and improve user experience. Such data may include personal information (e.g. IP, location, etc.)</string>
  <string name="disageement_abnormal_download">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
  <string name="disagree">Cancelar</string>
  <string name="disagreement_abnormal_running">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_application">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_product">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this product. You can choose not to use this product in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service. You can choose not to use this service in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_exit_app">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to sign out or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_function">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this feature. You can choose not to use this feature in such cases."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_location_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
  <string name="disagreement_terminate_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to uninstall, sign out, or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
  <string name="download_introduction">This app manages all your downloads, including those done in GetApps, Mi Video, Updater, Themes, and Browser.</string>
  <string name="enable_accessibility_canceled">Acessibilidade cancelada</string>
  <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_message">Ligou o TalkBack ao premir o ecrã com 2 dedos por mais de 10 segundos. O TalkBack fornece uma voz para pessoas invisuais. Se o ligou por acidente, toque no botao Cancelar e depois duplo toque no ecrã</string>
  <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_negative_btn">Cancelar</string>
  <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_positive_btn">OK</string>
  <string name="fast_application_introduction">Quick apps Framework allows you to create and provide services in quick apps.</string>
  <string name="font_hint_large">Tamanho do texto predefinido</string>
  <string name="font_hint_normal">Aumentar tamanho do texto</string>
  <string name="framework_introduction">Mi Services Framework allows you to use Mi Account, Mi Push, Mi Stats, and MIUI BI.</string>
  <string name="framwork_base_service">To provide you with these services, Mi Services Framework (MiAccount, Mi Push, Mi Stats, MIUI BI) needs to connect to the internet, access your phone number, IMEI, and IMSI, and allow your device to receive push notifications</string>
  <string name="game_introduction">Games plug-in allows you to sign in, create orders, complete payments, use coupons, and participate in promotion events.</string>
  <string name="google_service_introduction">To be able to work normally, Google Play needs to connect to the internet, access your location, be able to record audio, make calls, access calendar events, call history, sensors, storage, camera, device info, and accounts.</string>
  <string name="ime_privacy_policy">Política de Privacidade para o teclado seleccionado</string>
  <string name="ime_privacy_policy_no_network">Não é possível ligar à Internet. Ver a Política de Privacidade para este teclado em %s</string>
  <string name="input_method_category">Escolha o teclado predefinido para escrever emails ou notas. Pode instalar teclados de terceiros mais tarde</string>
  <string name="input_method_setting">Escolher teclado</string>
  <string name="install_preinstall_app">A carregar aplicações…</string>
  <string name="item_fingerprint">Impressão digital</string>
  <string name="item_lock_screen_password">Apenas bloqueio de ecrã</string>
  <string name="language_picker_other_languages_title">Mais idiomas</string>
  <string name="language_settings">Escolher idioma</string>
  <string name="locale_picker_title">Escolher a sua região</string>
  <string name="location_introduction">Location-based services find products and services near you.</string>
  <string name="lockscreen_introduction">Wallpaper Carousel allows you to get fresh images delivered to your Lock screen daily.</string>
  <string name="miui_privacy_policy_no_network">Sem ligação de rede. Ver Política de Privacidade em %s</string>
  <string name="miui_terms_no_network">Sem ligação de rede. Ver Termos de Utilização em %s</string>
  <string name="multisim_settings_category">Definições do cartão SIM</string>
  <string name="multisim_settings_title">Detectados 2 cartões SIM</string>
  <string name="navigation_picker_gesture_guide">Guia de gestos</string>
  <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_full_screen">Gestos de ecrã inteiro</string>
  <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_virtual_key">Botões</string>
  <string name="next">Seguinte</string>
  <string name="next_fingerprint">Seguinte</string>
  <string name="note_introduction">Esta aplicação permite criar, ver e editar notas</string>
  <string name="other_settings">Definições adicionais</string>
  <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_content">"Após desligar esta funcionalidade, não vai mais receber anúncios personalizados. Vai continuar a receber anúncios irrelevantes para si. Pode saber mais na Política de Privacidade da Xiaomi.
Desligar os anúncios personalizados mesmo assim?"</string>
  <string name="other_settings_ad_disable_summary">Ligar anúncios personalizados</string>
  <string name="other_settings_ad_enable">Anúncios personalizadoss</string>
  <string name="other_settings_ad_enable_summary">Personalizar anúncios com base nos seus interesses</string>
  <string name="other_settings_auto_update">Actualizações automáticas</string>
  <string name="other_settings_auto_update_summary">A MIUI vai seleccionar o melhor momento para instalar as actualizações. O seu dispositivo vai ser reiniciado automaticamente</string>
  <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen">Papéis de parede aleatórios</string>
  <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_privacy_index">Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary">Receber imagens e histórias seleccionadas diariamente no seu ecrã de bloqueio. %1$s e %2$s</string>
  <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary_index">Contrato de Licença do Utilizador</string>
  <string name="other_settings_location">Localização</string>
  <string name="other_settings_location_summary">Permitir que aplicações determinem a sua localização</string>
  <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_summary">As estatísticas de utilização que nos ajudam a localizar e resolver problemas podem conter informações pessoais</string>
  <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_title">Enviar dados de diagnóstico automaticamente</string>
  <string name="other_settings_user_experience">Programa de Experiência do Utilizador</string>
  <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary">Ajude-nos a melhorar os nossos produtos e serviços ao partilhar estatísticas de utilização</string>
  <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary_index">Ver detalhes</string>
  <string name="permission_account">Access accounts on your device:</string>
  <string name="permission_account_introduction">For signing in with Mi Account</string>
  <string name="permission_application_package_introduction">For accessing storage in order to parse and scan installation packages</string>
  <string name="permission_call_records">Access call history:</string>
  <string name="permission_call_records_introduction">For accessing call history in order to display blocked items</string>
  <string name="permission_call_state_introduction">For accessing phone status, recording calls, and pausing recordings during incoming calls</string>
  <string name="permission_clock_info_introduction">For saving alarm data</string>
  <string name="permission_contact">Access contacts:</string>
  <string name="permission_contact_introduction">For providing Blocklist functionality and calling emergency contacts</string>
  <string name="permission_different_device_introduction">For identifying services associated with different devices</string>
  <string name="permission_different_info_introduction">For identifying different devices</string>
  <string name="permission_direct_call">Make calls:</string>
  <string name="permission_direct_call_introduction">For adding items to Blocklist</string>
  <string name="permission_download_introduction">For caching downloaded items and saving them on your device</string>
  <string name="permission_imei_service">For accessing IMEI to provide services associated with your device</string>
  <string name="permission_interaction_introduction">For saving photos and videos on device</string>
  <string name="permission_location">Access location info:</string>
  <string name="permission_location_introduction">For providing location-based services</string>
  <string name="permission_log_introduction">For saving logs</string>
  <string name="permission_login_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
  <string name="permission_message_introduction">For sending messages to blocked contacts</string>
  <string name="permission_phone_imei_device">For accessing IMEI in order to identify devices</string>
  <string name="permission_phone_network">For accessing network type in order to optimize and adjust downloadable items</string>
  <string name="permission_phone_service">Access phone number, IMEI, and IMSI:</string>
  <string name="permission_photo_introduction">For saving images to Gallery and publishing statuses</string>
  <string name="permission_photo_video">Take photos and record video:</string>
  <string name="permission_photo_video_introduction">For taking photos, recording videos, and using flash</string>
  <string name="permission_picture_introduction">For saving, editing, and syncing photos and videos</string>
  <string name="permission_read_call_records">Edit call history:</string>
  <string name="permission_read_call_records_introduction">For adding items to call history and deleting blocked calls</string>
  <string name="permission_read_note_introduction">For accessing notes and attachments</string>
  <string name="permission_read_write_file">Access and save files and photos on your device:</string>
  <string name="permission_read_write_file_introduction">For accessing, saving, and caching items on your device</string>
  <string name="permission_recorder_file_introduction">For accessing and saving audio recordings</string>
  <string name="permission_recording">Record calls and audio:</string>
  <string name="permission_recording_introduction">For recording audio while recording video</string>
  <string name="permission_screen_shoot_introduction">For accessing and saving screen recordings</string>
  <string name="permission_send_message">Send SMS</string>
  <string name="permission_user_record_introduction">For recording audio</string>
  <string name="permission_virusscan_introduction">For performing virus scan and optimizing your device</string>
  <string name="permission_xunlei_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts in order to provide Xunlei services</string>
  <string name="pref_title_data_slot">Cartão SIM de dados preferido</string>
  <string name="pref_title_voice_slot">Cartão SIM de voz preferido</string>
  <string name="privacy_policy">Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="protect_persoanl_info_statement">We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies.</string>
  <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description">"
Ver Política de Privacidade do teclado seleccionado"</string>
  <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description1">Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="recorder_introduction">You can use this app to record audio and back up recordings to the cloud.</string>
  <string name="require_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
  <string name="require_network_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to connect to the internet and grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
  <string name="screen_recording_introduction">"This app allows you to record what's happening on your screen."</string>
  <string name="security_introduction">You can use this app to clear trash on your device, find and neutralize viruses, optimize performance for gaming, save battery, manage apps, and more.</string>
  <string name="security_mobile_account_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
  <string name="service_agreement">Eu li e concordei com os termos e condições</string>
  <string name="service_name_album">Galeria</string>
  <string name="service_name_application_package">Instalador de pacotes</string>
  <string name="service_name_calculator">Calculadora</string>
  <string name="service_name_camera">Câmara</string>
  <string name="service_name_carrier">Declaração sobre serviços da operadora</string>
  <string name="service_name_clock">Relógio</string>
  <string name="service_name_compass">Bússola</string>
  <string name="service_name_content_center">Centro de conteúdos</string>
  <string name="service_name_download">Transferências</string>
  <string name="service_name_fast_application">Aplicações rápidas</string>
  <string name="service_name_game">Plugin de jogos</string>
  <string name="service_name_google_service">Declaração sobre os serviços Google</string>
  <string name="service_name_location">Serviços baseados na localização</string>
  <string name="service_name_lockscreen">Papéis de parede aleatórios</string>
  <string name="service_name_note">Notas</string>
  <string name="service_name_recorder">Gravador</string>
  <string name="service_name_screen_recording">Gravador de Ecrã</string>
  <string name="service_name_security">Segurança</string>
  <string name="service_name_service_framework">Serviços Mi</string>
  <string name="service_policy">Leia e concorde com a nossa &amp;lt;a href=%1$s&amp;gt;Política de Privacidade&amp;lt;/a &amp;gt;</string>
  <string name="service_privacy_index">Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="servicestate_title">Declaração sobre serviços básicos</string>
  <string name="setting_locale">A definir região…</string>
  <string name="shut_down">Desligar</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detecting">A verificar o cartão SIM…</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detecting_check">Não foi possível localizar o cartão SIM. Certifique-se que o cartão SIM está devidamente colocado</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detecting_confirm_turn_on_network">Permitir a ligação a redes de dados móveis? Se permitir, o cartão SIM que inserir vai ser utilizado para ligar às redes de dados móveis</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detecting_title">A procurar cartão SIM</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detection">Insira o cartão SIM</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detection_info">Para inserir o cartão SIM, deve ler as instruções que acompanham o dispositivo</string>
  <string name="sim_card_detection_mobile_not_available">O cartão SIM não conseguiu ligar à rede</string>
  <string name="sim_dectection_next">Continuar</string>
  <string name="sim_redetection">Verifique o cartão SIM</string>
  <string name="sim_scard_detecting_check_mobile_not_available">O seu cartão SIM não conseguiu ligar a uma rede válida. Certifique-se que tem saldo e tente novamente</string>
  <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_message">Certifique-se que sabe utilizar os gestos de ecrã inteiro antes de seleccionar esta opção</string>
  <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_negative_btn">Cancelar</string>
  <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_positive_btn">OK</string>
  <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_title">Gestos de ecrã inteiro</string>
  <string name="skip_underline">Ignorar este passo</string>
  <string name="start_up_slogan">A vida torna-se mais fácil</string>
  <string name="summary_not_set">Não definido</string>
  <string name="system_navigation_mode">Modo de navegação do sistema</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use">Termos e condições</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_ble_htmlViewer">, Fornecedor de localização, Visualizador HTML</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label">"Read our User Agreement and Privacy Policy to understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices are available to you.
You must agree to our User Agreement and Privacy Policy before you can use MIUI.
%s and Mi Account components will connect to the internet and acquire your location."</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_Mistore">, Mi Store</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_mab">, MAB</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_package">, Instalador de pacotes</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_phrase">, Frases frequentes</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_systemhelper">, Serviços auto-registados</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_label_updater">, Actualizações</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_lable_apps">Mi services, Mi SIM activation services, Xiaomi Cloud, Find device, Home screen, Games, MIUI Daemon, MSA system components, translation services, Quick apps, App vault, statistics, Mi Link</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_facemoji">"

You must agree to Facemoji Privacy Policy before using this feature."</string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_lable_gms">, serviços Google Play </string>
  <string name="terms_of_use_lable_smart_cards">, Smart cards</string>
  <string name="title_fingerprint">Definir palavra-passe</string>
  <string name="user_agreement">Termos de Utilização</string>
  <string name="user_agreement_declare">Before using MIUI, you must read and agree to our User Agreement and Privacy Policy. While your device is being activated, Mi SIM Activation Service, Home screen, Frequent phrases, Translation Service, MIUI Daemon, and Updater will connect to the network. MSA will connect to the network and access your location.</string>
  <string name="voice_assist_condition">"You'll be able to use Mi AI in these cases:
1. When the screen is on.
2. When you're listening to music with your screen off."</string>
  <string name="voice_assist_desp">Diga \"Mi AI\" para o seu telefone. Mi AI vai reconhecer a sua voz e vai poder controlar o seu dispositivo</string>
  <string name="voice_assist_title">Ligar com voz</string>
  <string name="welcome">Bem-vindo</string>
  <string name="zone_picker_title">Escolher fuso horário</string>
</resources>
